{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "You ONLY want to manage Applications and Data. Which type of Cloud Computing model should you use?",
      "answers": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "On-premises" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Software as a Service (SaaS)" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Platform as a Service (PaaS)" }
      ],
      "correct": [4]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "What is the pricing model of Cloud Computing?",
      "answers": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Discounts over time" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Pay-as-you-go pricing" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Pay once a year" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Flat-rate pricing" }
      ],
      "correct": [2]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which Global Infrastructure identity is composed of one or more discrete data centers with redundant power, networking, and connectivity, and are used to deploy infrastructure?",
      "answers": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Edge Locations" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Availability Zones" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Regions" }
      ],
      "correct": [2]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT one of the Five Characteristics of Cloud Computing?",
      "answers": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Rapid elasticity and scalability" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Multi-tenancy and resource pooling" },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "text": "Dedicated Support Agent to help you deploy applications"
        },
        { "id": 4, "text": "On-demand self service" }
      ],
      "correct": [3]
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which are the 3 pricing fundamentals of the AWS Cloud?",
      "answers": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "text": "Compute, Storage, and Data transfer in the AWS Cloud"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "text": "Compute, Networking, and Data transfer out of the AWS Cloud"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "text": "Compute, Storage, and Data transfer out of the AWS Cloud"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "text": "Storage, Functions, and Data transfer in the AWS Cloud"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [3]
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which of the following options is NOT a point of consideration when choosing an AWS Region?",
      "answers": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Compliance with data governance" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Latency" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Capacity availability" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Pricing" }
      ],
      "correct": [3]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT an advantage of Cloud Computing?",
      "answers": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "text": "Trade capital expense (CAPEX) for operational expense (OPEX)"
        },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Train your employees less" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Go global in minutes" },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "text": "Stop spending money running and maintaining data centers"
        }
      ],
      "correct": [2]
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "AWS Regions are composed of?",
      "answers": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Two or more Edge Locations" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "One or more discrete data centers" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Three or more Availability Zones" }
      ],
      "correct": [3]
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which of the following services has a global scope?",
      "answers": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "EC2" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "IAM" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Lambda" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Rekognition" }
      ],
      "correct": [2]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which of the following is the definition of Cloud Computing?",
      "answers": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "text": "Rapidly develop, test and launch software applications"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "text": "Automatic and quick ability to acquire resources as you need them and release resources when you no longer need them"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "text": "On-demand availability of computer system resources, especially data storage (cloud storage) and computing power, without direct active management by the user"
        },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Change resource types when needed" }
      ],
      "correct": [3]
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "What defines the distribution of responsibilities for security in the AWS Cloud?",
      "answers": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "AWS Pricing Fundamentals" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "The Shared Responsibility Model" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "AWS Acceptable Use Policy" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "The AWS Management Console" }
      ],
      "correct": [2]
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "A company would like to benefit from the advantages of the Public Cloud but would like to keep sensitive assets in its own infrastructure. Which deployment model should the company use?",
      "answers": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Private Cloud" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Public Cloud" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Hybrid Cloud" }
      ],
      "correct": [3]
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "What is NOT authorized to do on AWS according to the AWS Acceptable Use Policy?",
      "answers": [
        { "id": 1, "text": "Building a gaming application" },
        { "id": 2, "text": "Deploying a website" },
        { "id": 3, "text": "Run analytics on stolen content" },
        { "id": 4, "text": "Backup your data" }
      ],
      "correct": [3]
    }
  ]
}
